Cleaned and corrected by Lunar Team
The victim is Felix Hanson, 47.
Took three bullets to the chest.
No weapon found.
Coroner estimates the shooting occurred
sometime between midnight and 3 a.m.
Why's this one ours?
Looks like a mugging.
- Hollywood Homicide can handle that.
- Came from the big brass.
Hanson was super rich and was a
California state representative for six years.
Golfing buddy of the attorney general?
Correct, but not quite fair.
Hanson was a good guy.
He headed a campaign
against the drug trade.
He kicked butt, named names,
and made a lot of enemies.
Wait a second, I know this guy.
He's semi-famous.
He was married to Felicia Scott.
- She left the movies for him.
- Felicia Scott?
Oh, come on, you know.
She's been in loads of movies.
Sudden Embrace, love that movie.
Okay, my point is,
if this is drug related...
...the A.G. Is gonna wanna use
all of his resources to close this case.
Did anybody hear shots,
see what happened?
Nobody's come forward so far.
But Marilyn Monroe
and Charlie Chaplin over there...
...were with Hanson when
the first officer arrived on the scene.
- Any kids?
- Daughter, 16.
Shame.
- How you doing?
- Good.
You didn't happen to pick up
a set of car keys off this guy, did you?
- Uh, no.
- Valet ticket?
- No, nothing in the pockets.
- Hm.
- Nobody walks in L.A.
- No, no, they don't.
So you didn't hear anything unusual?
Okay.
And where were you going
when you found the victim?
I don't speak.
In the movies, no.
But here in the real world, you speak.
- You just did.
- I'm saying nothing more.
Five hours we've been here.
For the umpteenth time,
I was going home from work.
- Victor was walking me to my car.
- And what is your work?
I'm Marilyn.
How's that your work?
I stand on the street, people take photos
of me and give me tips.
- Why?
- I don't know. Where are you from?
What are you staring at?
You. What's your real name?
- Norma Jean Baker.
- What's your real real name?
- Yolanda Quinn.
- Yolanda.
You don't actually look very much
like Marilyn at all.
You do this kind of work because you
feel a deep connection with her, yeah?
- I guess.
- Yeah.
She was a lonesome soul,
poor woman.
Longed for affection,
attention, acceptance.
She got it. She came out here,
she worked hard, and she struggled...
...and she got it, all the love
and respect that she longed for.
And you can too. You will.
You will, Yolanda,
if you do the right thing now.
What thing?
Hand over the valet ticket, Yolanda,
that you stole from the dead man.
- I haven't got any valet ticket.
- Then tell Charlie to hand it over.
Give him the ticket.
- Son of a bitch.
- Give it.
Thank you.
- Can we go?
- Sure.
I'll keep the cops at bay, you guys run.
- What?
- Run, run.
Go, go, go, run.
- Nice. I could arrest you for that.
- You'll never take me alive, copper.
- Seriously.
- Seriously, it's Marilyn and Charlie.
You wanna make a comedy arrest?
See your name written
in the Weird News section?
- Where did he valet?
- At Musso and Frank's down the block.
Go back to the restaurant,
go through their credit-card receipts.
Find out
who he was having dinner with.
Will do.
Uh, boss? Whoa.
So I guess it is drug-trade related,
but not in a good-guy way.
I want you to pull back
really, really slowly.
Then I want you to do a tilt up, okay?
We're gonna catch them
when they come to the window.
- Gabriel Fanning?
- Yeah, that's me.
CBI.
We wanna talk to you
about Felix Hanson.
Why? What did he do?
He died last night.
- What?
- Is there somewhere we can talk?
Yeah, back over here.
Last night at dinner with Felix...
...both your credit cards were charged
at 11:30.
- Stay at the restaurant much longer?
- No, we left soon after that.
We were having a good time...
...but I wanted to be up early.
- Tomorrow's the first day of production.
- What is the production?
Dozen Roses. I'm directing.
Felix financed the picture.
That's why we were having dinner.
We were celebrating his first foray
as a producer.
- How did he get into film producing?
- He's married to Felicia Scott.
- She's starring in the movie.
- Felicia Scott. Remind me.
Come on. Felicia Scott.
Love Times Two. Baby, You're Mine.
- Sudden Embrace.
Sounds familiar.
Those were all a while back, though.
She looks better now than she did then.
Or just as good anyhow.
So, what's this movie about?
A mother's quest to find good men
for her three daughters.
It's funny, it's moving...
- Can I read it?
- No, you can't read it.
- It's about family and redemption and...
- Gotcha.
Did you and Felix get along?
You ever have any arguments?
I loved him. Loved him.
So many people in this town are phonies,
but Felix Hanson, he was real.
Felix, if he didn't like something,
he'd say so.
- What in particular did he not like?
- Nothing.
I'm just saying, in general,
he was like that, real.
How much did he have invested
in the film?
Ten.
- Million? Of his own money?
- Yup. He was a brave man.
He was doing it all for Felicia, of course,
not just for the potential profits.
Did you two leave the restaurant
together?
- We walked out together, yeah.
- And was anybody waiting for him?
Didn't see anybody.
I parked my car down the street.
We shook hands and said goodbye.
Do you own a gun, Gabriel?
No. I like guns, but I'm afraid
of blowing my own head off.
- What do you think?
- Oh, he's lying.
They had an argument.
You go out to celebrate...
...with the man that financed your movie
and only pay half the dinner bill?
Van Pelt, we need Gabriel Fanning's
cell-phone records from last night.
Sure. And while I have you...
...the last number dialed
on Hanson's cell was blocked.
I had the phone company trace it.
- Belongs to a Frederick Ross.
- Who?
Oh, just a convicted felon with multiple
possession and assault charges.
Beautiful. Find out where he is
and have the boys pick him up.
Okay. Wait a minute. I know this guy.
- He's on that beer commercial.
- The one with the llama?
- What?
- This Ross guy. He must be an actor too.
You know that beer commercial
with the guy wearing the toga?
We're supposed to be surprised when
the toga gets caught in the elevator?
Yeah, that's him. Weird, huh?
Yeah. He should've stuck to his day job.
You have the address?
Yeah, okay, bye.
- Go pick him up.
- Yes, ma'am.
We're sorry for your loss.
How long were you two together?
We've been married
almost eight years now.
Where were you last night?
Palm Springs.
Felix insisted I have a spa weekend
before filming started.
And you?
At home.
Was there anybody in your husband's life
who posed a threat?
Somebody he didn't feel safe around?
- No.
- We found...
What was it that first attracted you
to your husband? Not his looks.
- Oh, really?
- Yeah, really. He's not your type.
And what is my type?
Oh. Uh...
Sporty bad boys
with a hidden masochistic streak.
- Uh-huh.
- Not too bright.
- Not even close.
- No, that was a bull's-eye.
So, what did you like about Felix?
His voice, his self-assurance.
I don't understand
how these questions are relevant.
No reason. Just curious.
We found a large bag of marijuana
and various other prescription drugs...
...in the trunk of your husband's car.
- Oh, that's absurd.
- Why?
Because Felix didn't do drugs, period.
They've been planted.
I'm straight edge. Have been for years.
Do you know anybody
named Freddie Ross?
No. Who is that?
It's mine.
There you go.
It's Gabriel's assistant.
He wants us to report to set
for rehearsals.
Tell him we'll be there on time.
I'm sure they would understand
if you don't go into work today.
Believe me, I would like to back out
of the whole project.
With Felix gone, there is no point.
But the insurance company
is holding me to my contract.
They won't even cover any delays.
And I don't wanna end up in court.
- You in the movie too?
- Kind of.
We gave her a small speaking role
as one of my daughters.
- Isn't that cute?
- Yeah.
Do you wanna be an actress?
Whatever.
Not anymore.
Honey, I know it's hard now...
...but one day you might be glad
you were part of something...
- ...that's so important to your father.
- Ha.
Huh?
He didn't think this film
was important?
No, he thought
Gabriel screwed up the script.
He wanted to back out of the film.
Don't be a drama queen.
He wasn't happy with the script,
but that's why he met with Gabriel:
To talk it through.
He wasn't gonna back out.
He may have threatened to back out
to get what he wanted...
...but that's how it works.
So who's the fella?
- Brandon.
- Brandon who?
- Brandon Fulton.
- Oh. You guys dating?
Dating? No. Maybe. Sort of.
That's so nerdy, dating.
Your stepmother doesn't like him?
- No. Thank you for not saying anything.
- Forget it.
We'll be seeing you, Sydney.
- Brandon Fulton.
- I'm on it.
Freddie Ross. Apartment 23.
Supposedly this guy's also an actor.
He was in that beer commercial.
- The one with the llama?
- No, the guy in the toga.
- Yeah?
- Yeah.
Stupid.
Nobody home.
- Stop. Police.
- Hey, hold it.
- Freddie Ross, CBI. Hey.
Stop!
Hey, get out of the car.
- Crap.
- It's okay, I got the plate.
Yeah, I just spoke to Minelli.
The warrant's on its way.
Okay, we'll wait here for it.
Yeah, search Ross' place.
The L.A.P.D. Should be...
Yeah, they've been helpful so far.
Shouldn't be long.
- All right.
- We'll keep you posted, boss.
Hey. Hey, kid, it's a closed set.
What does that mean?
- Hello?
- I'll call you back.
Okay.
Warrant's on its way.
This is a closed set. What's it mean?
- Closed set.
- I know, but they're from the CBI.
I don't care
if they're from a faraway galaxy.
This is a closed set, okay?
No gawkers, no fans.
- We're not fans.
- Well, I'm sort of a fan.
California Bureau of Investigation.
We need to speak with Gabriel Fanning.
Oh, he can't talk to you right now.
- It's regarding a murder investigation.
- I'm Mitch Cavanaugh, Gabriel's agent.
- Hey, Mitch. Good.
- How you doing? Hi.
I heard about what happened
to Hanson.
Tragic. He was such a cool guy, truly.
Trying to make a movie here, though.
Yeah, well,
we're trying to solve a homicide.
He can't talk to you right now.
You keep this up,
I'll have you arrested for obstruction.
That's unfortunate, but go ahead.
I understand, Mitch.
Gabriel's one of your top clients.
- You can't lose him.
- Right.
No choice, whatever he says.
He says jump, you jump.
Bullied at school, were you?
- I was not, actually.
- Sure you were.
Even after all these years,
you lie awake sometimes...
...thinking of all the ways you could
wreak revenge on your tormentors.
And now out of fear and avarice,
you let Fanning bully you the same way.
Mitch, it's the same way.
It's the same thing.
- You gotta get a life.
- Or get arrested.
Go ahead.
That was strong.
Look at the size of this thing.
Great. Mitch, you little scum-sucker.
Class A.
Do you have a prescription for these?
What is this? Come on. Jesus.
Sit down.
We have a few follow-up questions.
Didn't we do this?
I answered all your questions.
That was before we knew
you were a liar and a drug abuser.
I don't abuse drugs, I use them.
They're for creativity.
- But you don't deny being a liar.
- I didn't lie.
- I spun the truth a little bit, maybe.
- Try giving it to us straight.
Felicia blabbed, didn't she?
Stupid bitch.
Fine. Yes.
Hanson told me last night he was
pulling his money out of the movie.
Day before principal photography,
the schmuck.
Without his money,
production would shut down?
- Yes.
- This is your first feature in seven years.
Word on the street
is you're a little difficult to work with.
Oh, really?
Is that what the word on the street is?
Screw the word on the street.
I took some time out to recharge.
I've been exploring other aspects
of my life.
Narcotics and despair?
It's been tough, okay?
I've come very close
to having to take a TV gig.
So, yes, I'm extremely anxious
for this film to work. I need it to work.
- Hanson's death was convenient, then.
- Yeah, it was. It was.
And when you told me he was dead,
my heart leapt for joy.
- And then I felt terrible.
- And then you felt good again.
Listen, I'm an artist, okay?
I'm arrogant, I'm dishonest,
and I'm childish.
But you know what? I'm not stupid.
- I do not think I'm above the law.
- Gabe.
- Felicia's on set. Ready to go?
- Thanks, Mitch, you incompetent weasel.
- Wait.
- I have a movie to shoot.
And we've got a narcotics charge
we can't ignore.
Those aren't my drugs.
Those are Mitch's drugs.
Right, right. That's not Gabe's drugs,
that's my drugs.
Sorry, Gabe, I shouldn't have left them
around the trailer. How dumb is that?
Can I go, ma'am?
- Now go win an Oscar, Gabe.
- Yeah, yeah.
You're under arrest.
I thought we'd worked through
your doormat issues.
Tell Cho to squeeze him a little.
He knows things.
- No, I don't.
- Sure you do, Mitch.
You're not gonna like getting squeezed
by Cho.
- Action.
- Daisy, where are you?
- I'm home. I'm not feeling so good.
- Oh, but, pudding, you have to come.
Why? Why is it so important?
- Line.
- Rowan's on his way.
Rowan...
Rowan is on his way.
I called him and pretended to be you.
- Oh, Mom, no, you didn't.
- Oh, yes, I did. I'm sorry, pud.
Rowan's not even interested in me,
and I don't want him anymore anyway.
- I'm sorry. Sydney, honey. Honey.
- Cut.
You can't just read the lines, hon.
You have to be Daisy.
You have to be her.
I need your passion here, Sydney.
I'm working alone.
Okay.
Okay, let's pick it up
from where we left off.
- "Rowan doesn't need me."
- To pickup.
- Rolling. Speed.
- Quiet, people. Settle, please.
Action.
Rowan's not interested in me,
and I don't want him anymore anyway.
Oh, honey,
don't give up on your dreams so easily.
I know love can be tough,
but it's all we have and...
Hello?
Hello? Hello...? Oh, hi, Rowan.
Good morning, Mrs. Atkins.
- Daisy's not here. She's at home.
- Oh, that's all right.
It's actually you
that I wanted to speak with.
- Oh?
- What you said just now about love...
Cut. Great.
- That's a cut.
- Lovely. Okay.
Okay, everybody,
we're gonna go one more time.
Don't flinch before the slap.
You don't know it's coming.
She's taking a right old wallop at me.
It hurt.
Oh, I'm sorry
for feeling a little emotional today.
Gabriel,
this scene is still running really flat.
- But I have an idea...
- We're in a master.
We're really wide.
You're that big in the frame.
- We're gonna fix it in coverage, okay?
- I realize that.
I think it's an important establishing...
No, no, Gabriel, please.
This is an establishing moment...
- Die screaming, malignant harpy.
- I missed that. What?
You know what?
Let's take 10, folks, okay?
- Come on, princess, let's talk.
- Please. You know...
- I know, it's...
- No, I understand.
- Hey.
- You're good. You're a good actor.
- Thank you.
Must have been tough
when your dad took up with Felicia.
Replacing your real mother.
My real mom's in an alcoholic stupor
somewhere in New Jersey.
- I was happy to see her go.
- Why is it that...?
- Bye.
Bye.
It should be pretty dead.
So, what do you know, Mitch?
- Nothing.
- Jane says you know stuff.
- And he's always right, is he?
- Pretty much.
So this is one for the books. It's a first.
I got nothing for you.
Unlawful possession of drugs
puts you in line for actual prison time.
I doubt that,
but if you're right, so be it.
Really? So be it?
I'm told the pills actually belong
to your client, Gabe Fanning.
- No comment.
- You'll go to prison to protect Fanning?
"How good of an agent
is Mitch Cavanaugh?"
"He went to prison to protect a client."
Sounds pretty good to me.
To protect a client,
he became the servant...
...of a large and violent criminal.
How does that sound?
Look, I'm willing to speak to you
on any subject you care to mention...
...but on my life,
I don't know who killed Felix Hanson.
Give me some guidance here.
What do you want to know about?
- Frederick Ross.
- Ross? Freddie Ross, the drug dealer?
- What about him?
- Do you know where we can find him?
- Maybe.
- Give us Ross and you're free to go.
Charges expunged.
Deal.
There he is.
- I got the hoody.
- Hey.
Hey. Stop right there.
Gotcha.
Hey, stop.
Sydney Hanson.
Let's go.
It's good to see you again.
You know, in custody.
- How do you know Felix Hanson?
- I never met the man in my life.
He called your cell
minutes before he was shot.
- I was in bed.
- Can anyone attest to that?
- Bruce.
- Where can we find Bruce?
Probably on my kitchen floor...
...chewing on a pig's ear
that I left for him.
What did Hanson say
when he called you?
He told me to stay away
from his little girl.
- You sleeping with her?
- Come on. What is she, like 10?
Sixteen.
Whatever. I'm not a pervert.
I know her boyfriend.
He's the one who'd buy from me.
Brandon Fulton.
Little bad boy.
Hanson had them both followed.
Shazam. Led him right to me.
I really have to get a new system going.
You know, retail drugs is for suckers.
- So where's Brandon now?
- I don't know.
I mean, we never hung out
except for business.
Hanson found out
Brandon got Sydney hooked on drugs...
...and traced the drugs to you.
We should write that down.
You know, get a pitch together.
You got a murder, intrigue,
young love.
- Yeah, all we need is an ending.
- Hanson wanted to do damage.
If you killed him protecting yourself,
that's self-defense, justifiable homicide.
Thanks for the tip.
Can I call my lawyer now? Please?
- How long have you been using drugs?
- You sound like my father.
Your father wasn't gonna
throw you in juvie, was he?
That was your weed and pills in the car,
wasn't it?
You're the man, you figure it out.
Guess it made you pretty mad
when your dad took your drugs away.
Well, it's not the first time it happened,
and I can always get more.
- From Freddie Ross?
- From whoever.
- Where'd you meet Freddie?
- I don't know. Around.
- Freddie says Brandon hooked you up.
- Brandon's not like people say he is.
Actor, 19 years old, nine prior arrests.
DUI, drug possession,
disorderly conduct. Should I go on?
Why do women
love bad boys so much?
I don't get it. Why do they love them?
What do you think?
- Can I go now?
- In a minute.
Your parents forbade you
from seeing Brandon.
- Yes.
- Why didn't she like him?
You know,
they said he was a bad influence.
Did he make you do something?
We needed some cash,
so I took some stuff from the house.
- Like what?
- Like stuff. Money, some old gun, pills.
Gun? What kind of gun?
I don't know. A gun.
And Brandon sold it for cash.
Your parents stopped you
seeing your prince.
- That make you mad?
- Of course.
- So you just kept on seeing him?
- No. No, I have not seen him.
Phone records say
he's been calling your house regularly.
Well, that's not... That's... I don't...
I don't know, whatever.
- Where is he now?
- I don't know where he is.
You know, Brandon's not a bad kid.
He's just too old
and way too wild for Sydney.
She said she stole a gun along with
some other things from the house.
Yeah, it was some old Army thing
that Felix liked to keep around.
What caliber?
- Forty-five, I believe. Please, sit down.
- You didn't report the theft?
No. It was a foolish girl's mistake.
Your husband was murdered
with a .45.
No, that's a coincidence.
Sydney loved her father.
No.
- No.
- What about Brandon?
He's a mixed-up kid.
There's no malice in him.
You knew the drugs in Felix's car
were Sydney's all along.
Yes.
You're good. She... Wow.
Felix found the drugs a few days ago.
He was heartbroken
because she had promised to stop.
So we held on to them
while we debated what to do.
And now that Felix is gone,
what are you gonna do?
Forgive her. Show her love.
We all make mistakes...
...but we have the power
to give ourselves a second chance.
Do you know if Sydney and Brandon
were still seeing each other?
- Did you ask her?
- I did.
She said she hadn't seen him
since you banned him.
- Then I believe her.
- He has been calling this house regularly.
Sydney.
Brandon dropped out of sight
after the murder of your husband.
No, I...
I refuse to believe it. I refuse.
I need to see Sydney.
When can she come home?
She's on her way.
There's no charges
regarding the drug offense.
Oh, God.
Thank you so much for your kindness
and your understanding.
Thank you.
It's okay.
There's a lot of leeway in juvenile cases.
I'll always be very grateful.
She was some woman.
Make the mighty Agent Lisbon
blush like a schoolgirl.
Please. I did not.
- You know what I predict?
- Nope.
- Guess.
- Just tell me.
No, I think you should guess,
it's good for you.
I predict Brandon Fulton will pay a visit
to the Hanson residence this evening.
- You think? Wouldn't be too clever.
- Love is not blind, but it's often stupid.
I'll arrange a stakeout.
Oh, yeah, when I'm super rich,
I'm gonna live here.
Can't beat the sound
of the waves, huh?
They've got gadgets
that'll do that for you.
The sound of waves on the beach,
jungle sounds, roaring fire.
But it's not quite the real Pacific Ocean,
is it?
Cheaper.
In the event you don't become rich.
- Oh, I'll be rich. I'll be super rich.
- Right.
Hey. The eagle has landed.
Oh, crap, he's already in.
He must have keys.
Oh, God, help me. Oh, help me!
Help.
Drop the gun, ma'am.
Get back.
Have I killed him?
- Oh, God, is he dead? Have I killed him?
- This is Agent Cho, CBI.
We need paramedics
at 43565 Trancas Beach Road.
We got a juvie male
with a gunshot wound to the abdomen.
I just panicked. I just...
I saw the gun and I panicked.
Just panicked. Is he gonna be okay?
- Hey, .45.
- Nice. Is he okay?
- Hope so.
- What happened?
- Oh, my God, Brandon! Please.
- No, no. Hey, hey, hey.
- He's all right. He's all right. Come on.
- Please.
- What?
- Hey, boss.
Yeah, we got a good-news,
bad-news situation here.
Now, there are no guarantees,
but as of now...
...there won't be any charges pressed
against you for shooting Brandon.
Oh, thank goodness for that.
- Is he gonna be all right?
- Yeah, he'll be fine.
Well, that's a relief.
I mean, I feel terrible.
But what was he thinking,
sneaking around our house with a gun?
- What does he say he was doing?
- He's still recovering from surgery.
We're gonna talk to him
as soon as we can.
The gun he was carrying
is the gun that killed your husband.
It's the gun Sydney stole
from your house.
- Oh, my God.
- Yes.
Sydney may be an accessory
to murder.
Why were you there last night,
Brandon? What were you doing?
Before you Nazis shot me?
- I was visiting my girlfriend.
- We didn't shoot you.
Yeah, tell that to the judge.
I'm suing your ass bigtime.
Yeah, okay, that's a plan.
Here's your problem, Brandon.
The gun you were carrying
was the gun used to kill Felix Hanson...
...the gun Sydney stole for you.
Which puts you both
in a whole lot of trouble.
- I have nothing to say about that.
- Did Sydney know?
- Did she know what?
- You were gonna kill her father.
I didn't.
Did she ask you to do it?
- I didn't kill him.
- We know you killed him.
That ship has sailed.
We're charging you
with the murder of Felix Hanson.
We just wanna know
if Sydney's involved.
You people have no idea
who he really was.
He was a monster, a total sadist.
- A sadist?
- Whatever, man, he liked to hurt people.
That'd be a good reason to kill a man,
if he was hurting someone that you love.
Yeah, any man would do the same.
Did he hurt Sydney?
Is that what she told you?
Did she persuade you
that he needed to die, to protect her?
I'm saying nothing.
I want my lawyer.
Hey, boss.
He's lawyered up and admitting nothing.
Tough to get a conviction
with what we have.
- But we have the murder weapon.
- The gun's a double-edged sword.
It was never reported stolen.
- And we recovered it in Hanson's house.
- From Brandon.
We never saw it
in Brandon's possession.
No recoverable prints.
We can't put Hanson, the gun
and Brandon in the same place.
So without an actual confession
from Brandon, we're stuck.
Or a confession from Sydney.
There's no way that Brandon did this
without her say-so, right?
That, my dear,
is an excellent question.
- Is Brandon gonna be okay?
- He'll live.
I wanna see him. I need to talk to him.
- And what would you say to him?
- That's none of your business.
I think I know what happened here,
Sydney. I'm wondering if you do too.
Yeah, my boyfriend shot my dad,
then my stepmom shot my boyfriend.
- My life is a sick joke.
- So tell me, Sydney...
...why would Brandon kill your dad
unless you wanted him to?
Unless you asked him to?
- I didn't ask him to do anything.
- Can you look at me and say that?
I didn't ask him to do anything.
I loved my father. I did.
- Maybe someone else made him do it.
- Who?
You tell me.
What are you thinking?
I'm thinking Felicia and Sydney
should go back to work.
Oh, really? Why so?
A great man once said,
"All the world's a stage...
...and all the men and women
merely players."
- Oh, really?
- Really.
Ladies, good morning.
How are you?
- Fine.
- Okay.
I was thinking, before we roll...
...why don't we run through
the whole thing for fun?
- Sure.
- Don't worry about being on page.
Just use your instincts and let's see
what happens, okay? Alrighty.
Shoot it.
All right, everybody. This is rehearsal.
Rehearsal's up. Let's play it.
Okay, let's see how this goes.
- Settle, please.
- And action.
- Daisy, where are you?
- I'm right here, Mom.
Look at you. You look good.
Thanks.
What were you calling me about?
Just wanted to make sure
you were on your way.
Why is it so important I be here?
I did a naughty thing.
I called Rowan. He's on his way.
I pretended to be you.
- Oh, no, you didn't.
- Oh, yes, I did. I'm sorry, bunny.
Why would you do that?
I mean, why play games?
You've already seduced him
away from me.
I did not. Why would you say that?
Stop acting. It's over.
I know what you did.
I know who you are.
You've always hated me.
You seduced Brandon,
and you lied to him...
...and you made him kill my father.
- I... Gabe...
- No, you're not going anywhere.
- Gabe, cut it. She's gone mad.
- No.
I'll let you go
after you tell them it's not true.
Tell them I'm wrong. Tell them.
I... It's not true, it's...
No, it's not.
- It's not. It's not true.
- God, you're such a liar.
This is ridiculous.
I don't know what he said to you...
...but it's nonsense.
This is upsetting to me and unfair.
Sydney, terrific. Just terrific.
You, I'm not buying it.
You're wooden, high-pitched.
Believe it, Felicia.
Believe it and then we will, okay?
Let's try one more from,
"This is ridiculous."
Is this? No, I'm...
I'm sorry, I don't understand.
It's easy to understand.
You told Brandon
that Felix was abusing you.
You persuaded Brandon to kill Felix.
When you feared he'd confess
to the police...
...you lured him to the house
planning to kill him as well.
But now Sydney sees the truth.
She knows you're a conniving,
murderous bitch.
Way too melodramatic.
Your whole world is falling apart.
You're done unless you can convince us
that you are telling the truth now.
My... My work is always truthful.
There's a little afternoon soap in there.
That's a terrible thing to say.
Tell us the truth, Felicia.
Make it real.
You can do it.
Oh, God. I'm sorry.
What was that? Speak up.
- I'm sorry.
- For what?
I was angry.
He changed his mind
over script issues, he said.
He didn't want me out there
being successful...
...having other men look at me
and want me.
It made him feel insecure.
I gave up my life to be with him.
This is my life,
and he wouldn't let me have it back.
He was suffocating me.
It was a form of abuse.
Hey. Sydney here?
No, she's out.
Brandon came along
at a weak moment.
Why don't you come sit down
with me?
He forced himself on me.
I let him.
He told Felix
that Sydney was in trouble.
Felix went right along.
It's Sydney. She's back here.
She needs you.
Sydney!
What's going on here, Brandon?
You sick bastard.
He did love
that daughter of his. I'll give him that.
If only he could have accepted me
for who I am...
...respected my needs...
...this would never have happened.
Men are beasts.
- Patrick, would you do me a favor?
- Well, I might.
Tell Sydney that I'm sorry.
I see now, in reflection...
...I wasn't the stepmother
I might have been.
I'm sorry for that.
I did try.
God, I hope and pray
that she doesn't become bitter.
I hope that she finds happiness.
Because happiness is so hard to find.
Once you find it,
you've gotta hang on tight.
Or you will lose it.
That's true.